<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Bento</title>
    <link href="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar" />
    <updated>2022-09-15T11:41:43-03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Cesar</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Moving on, and away from commissions. </title>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/moving-on-and-away-from-commissions.html"/>
        <id>https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/moving-on-and-away-from-commissions.html</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T11:27:23-03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    I've been tru most of my time here, working on commissions, which has worked great but with some irremediable problems and issues that are making it harder for me to rely solely on it. The main advantage of commissions are that comms are a really&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/plan.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-xs.png 300w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-sm.png 480w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-md.png 768w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-lg.png 1024w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-xl.png 1360w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan-2xl.png 1600w"  alt="" width="720" height="360"></figure>
<p>I've been tru most of my time here, working on commissions, which has worked great but with some irremediable problems and issues that are making it harder for me to rely solely on it. </p>
<p>The main advantage of commissions are that comms are a really reliable almost 1:1 relation from work to income. If you ignore some road-bumps along the way. commissions are neatly delivering what you work on form of money. </p>
<p>But change is needed and I plan on investing more of my time in things that are not directly tied 1:1 with labour. Like making and selling VRChat avatars/bases and selling Environment models </p>
<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/plan2.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-xs.png 300w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-sm.png 480w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-md.png 768w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-lg.png 1024w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-xl.png 1360w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan2-2xl.png 1600w"  alt="" width="720" height="360"></figure>I don't actually plan on abandoning comm work right away. My goal until is to make comms 45%ish of the work I do, and asset (both environment and avatars) the remainder %. </p>
<p>and I really really hopes this pays out. Because as it is Commissions have a inalienable flaw for me to work on: My ADHD. and communication issues that goes with that. I am fairly decent on communicating in the start but keeping my clients updated tru and tru the process has been an overwhelming issue for me. That I don't see it being easy to solve alone. <figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/plan3.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-xs.png 300w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-sm.png 480w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-md.png 768w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-lg.png 1024w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-xl.png 1360w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/4/responsive/plan3-2xl.png 1600w"  alt="" width="720" height="360"></figure>
<p>But I don't plan to find a work partner anytime soon. and since I got some cushioning in money terms I am moving towards a more Sales based model. <br><br><strong>But what about you my client? </strong></p>
<p>If you have a commission open nothing will change for you. Absolutely nothing. I will deliver it and that is it. <br>For new commissions there will be some changes. </p>
<ul>
<li>First is that I will have a public queue with public updates<br>
<ul>
<li>Unless you want your model to be secret to which it will have special terms </li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Second my comms openings will be reduced from 5 to 2(or 3) and instead of opening it as soon as I finish an older one. This will be PER month. </li>
<li>And last, if I eventually find someone to help with this. all commission work will be turn into content. </li>
</ul>
<p>My terms and conditions will also be updated. For future models along with the licensing. But I really hope this works out and make for a better work environment. </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>A statement </title>
        <author>
            <name>Cesar</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/a-statement.html"/>
        <id>https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/a-statement.html</id>

        <updated>2022-09-15T11:41:43-03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    In the last few months I've had several mental health episodes due to my adhd that triggered depressive episodes. This has seriously impacted my work as well as my clients. Overall I've been able to navigate all punctual problems it caused but a small statement&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>In the last few months I've had several mental health episodes due to my adhd that triggered depressive episodes. This has seriously impacted my work as well as my clients. </p>
<p>Overall I've been able to navigate all punctual problems it caused but a small statement is necessary. </p>
<p>Some changes will be made so I don't burn out and so I can live of my art with tranquility in a healthy work environment. that means that I will be taking some parts of the work slowly. And this may impact you. </p>
<p>I am also looking forward to understand my limitations on working alone, and maybe finding someone to help me work and navigate client communication and organization. even if part time. But this is for the future. </p>
<p>Overall, thanks for all that stuck with me even if they didn't have to, and to those that didn't stuck y'all are valid and I am sorry to disappoint<figure class="post__image post__image--center"><img loading="lazy"  src="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/thanks.png" sizes="100vw" srcset="https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-xs.png 300w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-sm.png 480w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-md.png 768w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-lg.png 1024w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-xl.png 1360w ,https://gostbento.github.io/BentoCesar/media/posts/2/responsive/thanks-2xl.png 1600w"  alt="" width="720" height="360"></figure>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
